Finding Aid for College of Engineering (University of Michigan) Oral History Interviews, 2003
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
College of Engineering (University of Michigan) Oral History Interviews 2003
University of Michigan. College of Engineering.
17 audio cassettes.
2011113
Oral histories of University of Michigan College of Engineering faculty members, conducted by Enid Galler in 2003, discussing their background, education, careers, and the college and university
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The oral history interview tapes and transcripts were received from the University of Michigan College of Engineering (donor no. 1884 ) in December 2006.
Periodic additions to the records are expected.
The collection is open without restriction.
Oral history project conducted by Enid Galler in 2003 to document the history of the University of Michigan College of Engineering.
The University of Michigan College of Engineering Oral History Interviews are comprised of typed transcripts and audio cassette tapes of nine interviews with retired faculty members recorded during an oral history project undertaken by the college. The interviews were conducted by Enid H. Galler in 2003.
Interviews typically include information on the subject's background, education, and family, and commentary on his or her career and overall involvement with the university. The interviews also contain a great deal of information on the administration of, and issues within the College of Engineering, as well as on the operation of the university as a whole.
Subjects:
University of Michigan. College of Engineering.; University of Michigan--Faculty.
Subjects - Sound Recordings:
University of Michigan. College of Engineering.; University of Michigan--Faculty.
Contributors:
Adamson, Thomas Charles.; Balzhiser, Richard E.; Benford, Harry.; Buning, Harm Leopold.; Burks, Arthur W. (Arthur Walter), 1915-2008.; Duderstadt, James J., 1942-; Frey, Donald Welson.; Galler, Enid H.; Harden, Elaine.; Howe, Robert Milton, 1925-; Smith, Goff.; Wyman, Irma.
Genre Terms:
Oral histories.; Sound recordings.
- Transcripts
  - Tom Adamson, Harm Buning, Robert Howe, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Richard Balzhiser, 2003
  - Harry Benford, 2003
  - Arthur W. Burks, 2003
  - James Duderstadt, 2003
  - Donald N. Frey, 2003
  - Elaine Harden, 2003
  - Goff Smith, 2003
  - Irma Wyman, 2003
- Audiocassettes (Box 1)
  - Tom Adamson, Harm Buning, Robert Howe, March 2003, 2 tapes
  - Richard Balzhiser, April 2003, 2 tapes
  - Harry Benford, March 2003, 2 tapes
  - Arthur W. Burks, May 2003, 3 tapes
  - James Duderstadt, June, 2 tapes
  - Donald N. Frey, June 2003
  - Elaine Harden, June 2003, 2 tapes
  - Goff Smith, June 2003, 2 tapes
  - Irma Wyman, April 2003, 2 tapes